since its establishment in 1848 in a
different location, it has over 175 years of
experience in the Asian market, 20 years of
experience in the Vietnamese market
since 1999, started operating in 2002,
implemented a model with full rights to
Vietnamese banks in 2003, opened its
first general agency office in Long An.
Unlike other companies, it lacked a system in the
first linked insurance products
from across the industry, also making its first move in
2009, sales would become significant. Meanwhile, the
first foreign life insurance company, with
female employees spreading across 63 provinces and cities in
2015, lost the Vstar achievement recognition program
for students achieving
outstanding results.
Try using your passport to go to the agent and provide
more advice in 2016, embracing technological trends
with the love of time, we will launch the
first e-commerce in the
Vietnamese life insurance industry. To date, Truong Giang
will be the chairman, nurturing high-level
revolutions in the industry.  What kind of technique is this?
A good way you kiss her. Network
Dragon Mania launches a set of guidelines.
2017 Employer Recommendations launches a
talent development program by
specialization for IP. IP New Year in
the Wedding almonds launches the vijf product
and the collaborative image to partner with
Viettel in 2018. A
new leadership skills film with 6 key leadership competencies will be released.
All consulting staff
will implement building a diverse
and harmonious culture and gases and student at
Prudential. The
lottery results. The best way to beautify. Main
image. Consulting. Hau province. Protecting
Hung. 1.5 million customers like this, so
Cuong has 360 offices
nationwide. 20 years of development, more than anything in the
industry. What kind of staff and consulting?
2/12 2018 still lost 175 billion VND for the
community, focusing on 3 areas: education,
health and community support.
Second-class labor program by the President. Artificial intelligence.
16 consecutive years of business with
regulations.  Foreign investment insurance
in Vietnam, for several years from
2003 to 2019, won the
award for the 100 Best Places to Work in
Vietnam. It will also receive 25 awards, including
certification as one of the
deadliest workplaces in Asia, according to al al and those
things that went down to the ground. We think of you
guys,
319. There are times when remembering things is
similar, many things are also good things.